A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication, 1996-2004 FA1103A
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication
1996-2004
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
Medical Letter, Inc
FA1103A
131.21 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 25 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
File Plan
Former Classification: I 891-U
Other Finding Aids
For additional Medical Letter materials open for research see:
FA241 Rockefeller University collection of the Medical Lettter publication
Scope and Contents
Contents includes: original manuscripts, reprints, advertising and package inserts, sources check, consultatnts drafts, manufacturers replies, and bibliography.
Biographical / Historical
The Medical Letter on Drugs and Therapeutics is an independent, non-profit publication providing unbiased critical evaluation of drugs in terms of their effectiveness, adverse effects and possible alternative medications.
- TML, 38-9 - Acarbose for diabetes mellitus, 1996 February 2 (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted material - Open in 2022
- TML, 38-55 - Acetaminophen, NSAIDs and Alcohol, 1996 June 21 (Box 1, Folder 5-7)
- TML, 38-43 - Acute reactions to Drugs of Abuse, 1996 May 10 (Box 1, Folder 8-12)
- TML, 38-35 - New drugs for HIV, 1996 April 12 (Box 1, Folder 13-17)
- TML, 38-99 - Alteplase for thrombolysis in acute ischemic stroke, 1996 November 8 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- TML, 38-99 - Alteplase for thrombolysis in acute ischemic stroke, 1996 November 8 (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 38-61 - Anatrozle for metastatic breast cancer, 1996 July 5 (Box 2, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 38-25 - Choice of Antimicrobial Drugs, 1996 March 29 (Box 2, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 38-52 - Drugs for Cardiac Arrythmias, 1996 August 30 (Box 2, Folder 10-16)
- TML, 38-52 - Azelaic acid a new topical drug for acne, 1996 June 7 (Box 2, Folder 17-18)
- TML, 38-56 - Bicalutamide for prostate cancer, 1996 June 21 (Box 2, Folder 19-20)
- TML, 38-56 - Bicalutamide for prostate cancer, 1996 June 21 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- TML, 38-103 - Bone Density Testing, 1996 November 26 (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
- TML, 37-109 - Dirithromycin, 1995 November 24 (Box 3, Folder 4-7)
- TML, 38-108 - Calcium Supplements, 1996 December 6 (Box 3, Folder 8-12)
- TML, 38-40 - Radiofrequency cather abilation for treatment of cardiac arrhythmias, 1996 April 26 (Box 3, Folder 13-16)
- TML, 38-23 - Cetibuten - a new oral cephalosporin, 1996 March 15 (Box 3, Folder 17-19)
- TML, 38-84 - Cefepime (Maxime) - a new parenteral cephalosporin, 1996 September 13 (Box 4, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 38-46 - Chlorzoxazone hepatotoxsicity, 1996 May 10 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- TML, 38-67 - Choice of Lipid-Lowering drugs, 1996 August 2 (Box 4, Folder 6-13)
- TML, 38-21 - Cetirizine - a new antihistamine, 1996 March 15 (Box 4, Folder 14-18)
- TML, 38-109 - Clonidine for treatment of ADHD, 1996 December 6 (Box 4, Folder 19-20)
- TML, 38-109 - Clonidine for treatment of ADHD, 1996 December 6 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- TML, 38-64 - Dexfenfluramine for obesity, 1996 July 19 (Box 5, Folder 2-5)
- TML, 38-87 - Docetaxel (Taxotere) for advanced breast cancer, 1996 September 27 (Box 5, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 38-14 - Epoprostenol for primary pulmonary hypertension, 1996 February 16 (Box 5, Folder 9-10)
- TML, 38-95 - Fexofenadine, 1996 October 25 (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
- TML, 37-13 - Fluvoxamine for obsessive compulsive disorder, 1995 February 17 (Box 5, Folder 13-16)
- TML, 38-83 - Fluticasone propionate for chronic asthma, 1996 September 13 (Box 5, Folder 17-21)
- TML, 38-83 - Fluticasone propionate for chronic asthma, 1996 September 13 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- TML, 38-10 - Systematic antifungal drugs, 1996 February 2 (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
- TML, 38-102 - Gemcitabine for treatment of pancreatic cancer, 1996 November 8 (Box 6, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 38-47 - Glimepiride for NIDDM, 1996 May 24 (Box 6, Folder 7-8)
- TML, 38-92 - Drugs for chronic heart failure, 1996 October 11 (Box 6, Folder 9-13)
- TML, 37-73 - Grapefruit juice interactions with drugs, 1995 August 18 (Box 6, Folder 14-16)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Cardiac Arrhythmias, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 17-20)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Cardiac Arrhythmias, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Pain, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 3-7)
- TML, 37-95 - OTC H2 Blockers for heartburn, 1995 October 27 (Box 7, Folder 8-10)
- TML, 38-6 - Rho (D) IV Immune Globulin, 1996 January 19 (Box 7, Folder 11-13)
- TML, 38-17 - Advice for Travelers, 1996 March 15 (Box 7, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 37-98 - Influenza Vaccine, 1995-1996, 1995 September 1 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- TML, 38-86 - Influenza Vaccine, 1996-1997, 1996 September 13 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- TML, 38-59 - Oral hypnotic drugs, 1996 July 5 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- TML, 38-59 - Oral hypnotic drugs, 1996 July 5 (Box 8, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 38-63 - Interferon beta IA for relapsing multiple sclerosis, 1996 July 19 (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
- TML, 38-5 - Intraconazole for onychomycosis, 1996 January 19 (Box 8, Folder 7-10)
- TML, 38-100 - Latanoprost - A topical prostaglandin for glaucoma, 1996 November 8 (Box 8, Folder 11-14)
- TML, 38-97 - Lispro - A rapid onset insulin, 1996 October 25 (Box 8, Folder 15-16)
- TML - HAT, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 17-18)
- TML - HAT, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 38-13 - Nisoldipine - a new calcium-channel blocker for hypertension, 1996 February 16 (Box 9, Folder 4-7)
- TML, 35-62 - Nedocromil for asthma, 1993 July 9 (Box 9, Folder 8-12)
- TML, 38-1 - New drugs for osteoporosis, 1996 January 5 (Box 9, Folder 13-18)
- TML, 38-53 - Prostatron, 1996 June 7 (Box 9, Folder 19-20)
- TML, 38-107 - Pallidotomy for Parkinson's Disease, 1996 December 6 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 38-57 - Simethicone for gastrointestinal gas, 1996 June 21 (Box 10, Folder 4-5)
- TML, 38-106 - Sodium Phenylbutyrate for urea cycle enzyme deficiencies, 1996 November 22 (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
- TML, 38-72 - Terabinafine for onychomycosis, 1996 August 16 (Box 10, Folder 8-11)
- TML, 38-49 - Androderm (Testosterone patches), 1996 May 24 (Box 10, Folder 12-15)
- TML, 38-96 - Toptecan hydrochloride for metastic ovarian cancer, 1996 October 25 (Box 10, Folder 16-18)
- TML, 38-3 - Valacyclovir, 1996 January 5 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- TML, 38-3 - Valacyclovir, 1996 January 5 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 38-104 - Trandolapril - An ACE inhibitor for treatment of hypertension, 1996 November 22 (Box 11, Folder 3-5)
- TML, 38-71 - Umbilical cord blood for bone marrow transplantation, 1996 August 16 (Box 11, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 38-51 - Clarithromycine and omeprazole of helliobacter pylori, 1996 June 7 (Box 11, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 38-15 - New Uses of Thalidomide, 1996 February 16 (Box 11, Folder 12-14)
- TML - Antiviral drugs - Viral Infections (Non-HIV) Handbook, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 15-19)
- TML - Antiviral drugs - Viral Infections (Non-HIV) Handbook, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 38-65 - Drugs past their expiration date, 1996 July 19 (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 38-38 - Ibutilide, 1996 April 12 (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
- TML, 38-91 - DHEA, 1996 October 11 (Box 12, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 38-88 - Meropenem - A new parenteral broad-spectrum antibiotic, 1996 September 27 (Box 12, Folder 10-14)
- TML, 38-39 - Methotrexate and Misoprostol for abortion, 1996 April 26 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- TML, 38-111 - Zafirlukast for asthma, 1996 December 20 (Box 12, Folder 16-18)
- TML, 31-83 - Samarium 153 lexidronam for painful bone metastases, 1997 August 29 (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
  Restricted material - Open in 2023
- TML, 38-69 - Drugs for non-HIV viral infections, 1997 August 1 (Box 13, Folder 4-12)
- TML, 39-18 - Zileuton for asthma, 1997 February 28 (Box 13, Folder 13-14)
- TML, 39-9 - Zinc for the common cold, 1997 January 31 (Box 13, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 39-78 - Topical drugs for aging skin, 1997 August 15 (Box 13, Folder 18-20)
- TML, 39-78 - Topical drugs for aging skin, 1997 August 15 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- TML, 39-80 - Ropivocaine - a new local anesthetic, 1997 August 15 (Box 14, Folder 2-4)
- TML, 39-41 - Levofloxacin and sparfloxacin, 1997 April 25 (Box 14, Folder 5-10)
- TML, 39-10 - Lasers in dermatologic surgery, 1997 January 31 (Box 14, Folder 11-15)
- TML, 39-84 - Skin surgery with lasers - an additional note, 1997 August 29 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- TML, 39-51 - Topiramate for epilepsy, 1997 May 23 (Box 14, Folder 17-19)
- TML, 39-96 - Tamsulosin for prostatic benign hyperplasis, 1997 October 10 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- TML, 39-96 - Tamsulosin for prostatic benign hyperplasis, 1997 October 10 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 39-65 - Tiludronate for Paget's disease of bone, 1997 July 18 (Box 15, Folder 3-5)
- TML, 39-62 - Tizanidine for spasticity, 1997 July 4 (Box 15, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 39-49 - Troglitazone for non-insulin-dependent diabetes mellitus, 1997 May 23 (Box 15, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 39-43 - Valsartan for hypertension, 1997 April 25 (Box 15, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 39-1 - Drugs for treatment of peptic ulcers, 1997 January 3 (Box 15, Folder 15-20)
- TML, 39-109 - Pramipexole and Ropinirole for Parkinson's disease, 1997 November 21 (Box 16, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 39-105 - New drugs for psoriasis, 1997 November 7 (Box 16, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 39-33 - New drugs for psychiatric disorders, 1997 April 11 (Box 16, Folder 9-15)
- TML, 39-117 - Quetiapine for schizophrenia, 1997 December 19 (Box 16, Folder 16-18)
- TML, 39-17 - Reteplase (Retavase), 1997 February 28 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 39-53 - Donepezil (Aricept) for Alzheimer's disease, 1997 June 6 (Box 17, Folder 3-5)
- TML, 39-81 - Diagnostic tests for HIV, 1997 August 29 (Box 17, Folder 6-10)
- TML, 39-21 - Drugs of Choice - Cancer Chemotherapy, 1997 March 14 (Box 17, Folder 11-16)
- TML, 39-77 - Bupropion for smoking cessation, 1997 August 15 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- TML, 39-63 - Topical butenafine for tinea pedis, 1997 July 4 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 39-56 - Pentosan, 1997 June 6 (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 39-103 - Mibefradil - a new calcium-channel blocker, 1997 November 7 (Box 18, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 39-59 - Midodrine for orthostatic hypotension, 1997 June 20 (Box 18, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 39-47 - Treatment of Lyme disease, 1997 May 9 (Box 18, Folder 12-14)
- TML - Drugs of Choice, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 39-85 - Influenza vaccine, 1997 September 12 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- TML, 39-8 - Irinotecan for metastatic colorectal cancer, 1997 January 17 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- TML, 39-8 - Irinotecan for metastatic colorectal cancer, 1997 January 17 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- TML, 39-118 - Imiquimod for genital warts, 1997 December 19 (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
- TML, 39-64 - Drugs for epilepsy, 1997 February 6 (Box 19, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 39-66 - Fosfomycin for urinary tract infections, 1997 July 18 (Box 19, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 39-86 - Systemic antifungal drugs, 1997 September 12 (Box 19, Folder 10-13)
- TML, 39-61 - Glatiramer acetate for relapsing mutiple sclerosis, 1997 July 4 (Box 19, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 38-6 - Drugs for head lice, 1997 January 17 (Box 19, Folder 17-18)
- TML, 39-91 - Glucosamine for osteoarthritis, 1997 September 26 (Box 19, Folder 19-20)
- TML, 39-91 - Glucosamine for osteoarthritis, 1997 September 26 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 39-94 - Drugs for hypertension, 1997 November 1 (Box 20, Folder 3-5)
- TML, 39-19 - Adapalene for acne, 1997 February 28 (Box 20, Folder 6-7)
- TML, 39-29 - Atorvastatin - a new lipid-lowering drug, 1997 March 28 (Box 20, Folder 8-9)
- TML, 39-45 - Azelastine nasal spray for allergic rhinitis, 1997 May 9 (Box 20, Folder 10-13)
- TML, 39-12 - Betaine for homocystinuria, 1997 January 31 (Box 20, Folder 14-15)
- TML, 39-93 - Bromfenac for analgesia, 1997 October 10 (Box 20, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 39-54 - Brimonidine - an alpha2-agonist for glaucoma, 1997 June 6 (Box 20, Folder 18-19)
- TML, 39-13 - Safety of channel blockers, 1997 February 14 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- TML, 39-13 - Safety of channel blockers, 1997 February 14 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 39-58 - Cabergoline for hyperprolactinemia, 1997 June 20 (Box 21, Folder 3-6)
- TML - Dovonex, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- TML, 39-108 - Olopatadine for allergic conjunctivitis, 1997 November 21 (Box 21, Folder 8-9)
- TML, 37-1 - Drugs for asthma, 1996 January 6 (Box 21, Folder 10-14)
- TML, 39-32 - Intra-transurethral Alprostadil for impotence, 1997 March 28 (Box 21, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 39-14 - More new drugs for AIDS and associated infections, 1997 February 14 (Box 21, Folder 17-21)
- TML, 39-14 - More new drugs for AIDS and associated infections, 1997 February 14 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 39-111 - AIDS - Drugs for HIV infection, 1997 December 12 (Box 22, Folder 4-9)
- TML, 39-97 - Antimicrobial prophylaxis in surgery, 1997 October 24 (Box 22, Folder 10-15)
- TML, 39-120 - Anagrelide for essential thrombocythemia, 1997 December 19 (Box 22, Folder 16-18)
- TML, 39-94 - Ardeparin and danaparoid for prevention of deep vein thrombosis, 1997 October 10 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- TML, 39-94 - Ardeparin and danaparoid for prevention of deep vein thrombosis, 1997 October 10 (Box 23, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 39-89 - Carvedilol for heart failure, 1997 September 26 (Box 23, Folder 5-9)
- TML, 39-57 - Topical penciclovir for herpes labialis, 1997 June 20 (Box 23, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 38-17 - Drugs for migraine, 1995 March 3 (Box 23, Folder 12-16)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Drugs for Pain, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 17-21)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Drugs for Pain, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Parkinson's Disease, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 2-3)
- TML, 38-5 - Olanzapine for schizophrenia, 1997 January 17 (Box 24, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 38-113 - Mirtazapine - a new anti-depressant, 1996 December 20 (Box 24, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 40-5 - Drugs of Choice - Rheumatoid Arthritis, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 10-16)
- TML, 40-59 - Clopidogrel for reduction of artherosclerotic events, 1998 June 5 (Box 25, Folder 1-3)
  Restricted material - Open in 2024
- TML, 40-113 - Citalopram for depression, 1998 December 4 (Box 25, Folder 4-8)
- TML, 40-52 - Anthrax vaccine, 1998 May 8 (Box 25, Folder 9-10)
- TML, 40-63 - Ginkgo Biloba for dementia, 1998 June 19 (Box 25, Folder 11-13)
- TML, Sildenafil - Reprints, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 40-69 - Hyaluronan injections for osteoarthritis of the knee, 1998 July 3 (Box 25, Folder 17-19)
- TML, 40-57 - Fenoldopam - Severe Hypertension, 1998 May 22 (Box 25, Folder 20-21)
- TML, 40-57 - Fenoldopam - Severe Hypertension, 1998 May 22 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- TML, 40-21 - Drugs that cause psychiatric symptoms, 1998 February 13 (Box 26, Folder 2-5)
- TML, 40-47 - Advice for Travelers, 1998 April 24 (Box 26, Folder 6-9)
- TML, 40-68 - Fenofibrate, 1998 July 3 (Box 26, Folder 10-13)
- TML, 40-30 - Trovafloxacin, 1998 March 13 (Box 26, Folder 14-16)
- TML - Tuberculosis - HAT, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 17-18)
- TML - Tuberculosis - HAT, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 40-51 - Sildenafil - An oral drug for impotence, 1998 May 8 (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 40-67 - Sucralose - a new artificial sweetner, 1998 July 3 (Box 27, Folder 5-7)
- TML, 40-17 - Grepafloxacin - a new fluoroquinolone, 1998 January 30 (Box 27, Folder 8-9)
- TML, 40-55 - Repaglinide for type 2 diabetes mellitus, 1998 May 22 (Box 27, Folder 10-12)
- TML, 40-62 - Crystal Ear hearing aid, 1998 June 5 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- TML, 40-89 - Antiplatelet, 1998 September 11 (Box 27, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 40-109 - New drugs for rheumatoid arthritis, 1998 November 20 (Box 27, Folder 17-19)
- TML, 40-109 - New drugs for rheumatoid arthritis, 1998 November 20 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- TML, 40-65 - Rituximab for non-hodgkins lymphoma, 1998 June 19 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- TML, 40-32 - Sibutramine for obesity, 1998 March 13 (Box 28, Folder 3-5)
- TML, 40-27 - Zolmitriptan for migraine, 1998 February 27 (Box 28, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 40-73 - Becaplermin - Platelet-derived growth factor for diabetic ulcers, 1998 July 17 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- TML, 40-19 - Arbutamine for stress testing, 1998 January 2 (Box 28, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 40-75 - Vitamin supplements, 1998 July 31 (Box 28, Folder 12-16)
- TML, 40-92 - Gliadel wafers for treatment of brain tumors, 1998 September 11 (Box 28, Folder 17-18)
- TML - HAT, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- TML - HAT, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 1-5)
- TML, 40-106 - Trastuzumab for metastatic breast cancer, 1998 November 6 (Box 29, Folder 6-7)
- TML, 40-114 - Three new drugs for HIV infection, 1998 December 4 (Box 29, Folder 8-11)
- TML, Sexually Trasmitted Diseases - HAT, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 40-53 - Dolasetron, 1998 May 8 (Box 29, Folder 15-18)
- TML, 40-18 - Irbesartan for hypertension, 1998 January 30 (Box 30, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 40-33 - The Choice of Antibacterial Drugs, 1998 March 27 (Box 30, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 40-93 - New monoclonal antibodies to prevent transplant rejection, 1998 September 25 (Box 30, Folder 9-12)
- TML, 40-117 - Choice of lipid-lowering drugs, 1998 December 18 (Box 30, Folder 13-16)
- TML - Drugs for Parasitic Infections, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 17-19)
- TML - Drugs for Parasitic Infections, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 40-43 - Toremifene and Letrozole for advance breast cancer, 1998 April 10 (Box 31, Folder 4-8)
- TML, 40-95 - Brinzolamide for glaucoma, 1998 September 25 (Box 31, Folder 9-10)
- TML, 40-45 - Tigabine for epilepsy, 1998 April 10 (Box 31, Folder 11-13)
- TML, 40-64 - A new rabies vaccine, 1998 June 14 (Box 31, Folder 14-15)
- TML, 40-29 - Raloxifene for postmenopausal osteoporosis, 1998 March 13 (Box 31, Folder 16-18)
- TML, 40-60 - Tolcapone for Parkinson's disease, 1998 June 5 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- TML, 40-60 - Tolcapone for Parkinson's disease, 1998 June 5 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 40-15 - Budesonide turbuhaler for asthma, 1998 January 16 (Box 32, Folder 3-8)
- TML - Cholesterol-Lowering - Reprints, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 9-10)
- TML - Parasitic Infections - Reprints, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 11-14)
- TML - Malaria - Drugs for parastic infections, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 15-16)
- TML - Antimicrobial drugs - Reprints, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- TML - Antimicrobial drugs - Reprints, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
- TML - Psychiatric Symptoms - Reprints, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- TML, 40-109 - Candesartan, 1998 November 20 (Box 33, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 40-77 - Interleukin-11, 1998 July 31 (Box 33, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 40-85 - Cefdinir, 1998 August 28 (Box 33, Folder 10-12)
- TML, 40-79 - Drugs for pain, 1998 August 14 (Box 33, Folder 13-17)
- TML, 40-87 - Risedronate, 1998 August 28 (Box 33, Folder 18-19)
- TML, 40-87 - Risedronate, 1998 August 28 (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 40-94 - Lepirudin for heparin-induced thrombocytopenia, 1998 September 25 (Box 34, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 40-25 - Propecia and Rogaine Extra Stength for Alopecia, 1998 February 27 (Box 34, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 40-106 - Capecitabine for metastatic breast cancer, 1998 November (Box 34, Folder 9-10)
- TML, 40-13 - Cerivastatin for hypercholesterolemia, 1998 January 16 (Box 34, Folder 11-13)
- TML, 40-101 - Tolterodine for overactive bladder, 1998 October 23 (Box 34, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 40-102 - An Emergency Contraceptive Kit, 1998 October 23 (Box 34, Folder 17-18)
- TML, 40-71 - Montelukast for persistent asthma, 1998 July 17 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- TML, 40-71 - Montelukast for persistent asthma, 1998 July 17 (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 40-103 - Thalidomide, 1998 October 23 (Box 35, Folder 3-6)
- TML, 40-97 - New Triptans and other drugs for migraine, 1998 October 9 (Box 35, Folder 7-12)
- TML, 40-91 - Influenza vaccine, 1998-1999, 1998 September 11 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- TML, 40-105 - Creatine and Androstenedione - two "dietary supplements", 1998 November 6 (Box 35, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 39-107 - St. John's Wort, 1997 November 21 (Box 35, Folder 17-18)
- TML, 41-73 - Malathion for treatment of head lice, 1999 August 13 (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
  Restricted material - Open in 2025
- TML, 41-39 - Advice for travelers, 1999 April 23 (Box 36, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 41-30 - Modafinil for narcolepsy, 1999 March 26 (Box 36, Folder 5-7)
- TML, 41-51 - Levalbuterol for asthma, 1999 June 4 (Box 36, Folder 8-10)
- TML, 41-16 - Mometasone furoate nasal spray for allergic rhinitis, 1999 February 12 (Box 36, Folder 11-12)
- TML, 41-50 - Vaccine for rotavirus, 1999 May 21 (Box 36, Folder 13-14)
- TML, 41-91 - Two neuraminidase inhibitors for treatment of influenza, 1999 October 8 (Box 36, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 41-93 - Zaleplon for insomnia, 1999 October 8 (Box 37, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 41-1 - Tamoxife for the prevention of breast cancer, 1999 January 1 (Box 37, Folder 5-6)
- TML, 41-123 - Temozolomide, 1999 December 17 (Box 37, Folder 7-8)
- TML, 41-53 - Interferon plus ribavirin for chronic hepatitis C, 1999 June 4 (Box 37, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 41-49 - Miglitol for Type 2 diabetes mellitus, 1999 May 21 (Box 37, Folder 12-13)
- TML, 41-110 - Rabeprazole, 1999 November 9 (Box 37, Folder 14-15)
- TML, 41-21 - Rifapentine for tuberculosis, 1999 February 26 (Box 37, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 41-109 - Quinupristin (Dalfopristin), 1999 November 19 (Box 37, Folder 18-19)
- TML, 41-71 - Rosiglitazone for Type 2 diabetes mellitus, 1999 August 13 (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Rheumatoid Arthritis, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 4-7)
- TML, 41-59 - Rofecoxib for osteoarthritis and pain, 1999 July 2 (Box 38, Folder 8-10)
- TML, 41-84 - Pneumococcal vaccine, 1999 September 10 (Box 38, Folder 11-13)
- TML, 41-20 - Homeopathic products, 1999 February 26 (Box 38, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 41-55 - Orlistat for obesity, 1999 June 18 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- TML, 41-69 - Prosorba column for rheumatoid arthritis, 1999 July 30 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- TML, 41-23 - Drugs for hypertension, 1999 March 12 (Box 39, Folder 1-6)
- TML, 41-113 - Drugs for non-HIV viral infection, 1999 December 3 (Box 39, Folder 7-10)
- TML, 41-112 - Pioglitazone (Actos), 1999 November 19 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- TML, 41-43 - Suncreens - Are they safe and effective, 1999 May 7 (Box 39, Folder 12-16)
- TML, 41-56 - Cholesterol-lowering margarines, 1999 June 18 (Box 39, Folder 17-18)
- TML, 41-56 - Cholesterol-lowering margarines, 1999 June 18 (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 41-105 - A new ACE inhibitorand two new angiotensin receptor blockers for hypertension, 1999 November 5 (Box 40, Folder 3-6)
- TML, 41-67 - A new conjugated estrogen, 1999 July 30 (Box 40, Folder 7-8)
- TML, 41-15 - Drugs and vaccines against biological warfare, 1999 February 12 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- TML, 41-68 - Laser hair removal, 1999 July 30 (Box 40, Folder 10-11)
- TML - Drugs of Choice - Parkinson's Disease, 1999 (Box 40, Folder 12-16)
- TML, 41-5 - Drugs for Asthma, 1999 January 15 (Box 41, Folder 1-5)
- TML, 41-12 - Drugs for chronic heart failure, 1999 January 29 (Box 41, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 41-32 - Valrubicin for bladder cancer, 1999 March 26 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- TML, 41-19 - Infliximab (Remicade) for Crohn's disease, 1999 February 26 (Box 41, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 41-82 - Influenza vaccine, 1999-2000, 1999 September 10 (Box 41, Folder 12-13)
- TML, 41-81 - Spironolactone for heart failure, 1999 September 10 (Box 41, Folder 14-15)
- TML, 41-2 - Growth-hormone-releasing factor for growth hormone deficiency, 1999 January 1 (Box 41, Folder 16-18)
- TML, 41-18 - Saw Palmetto for benign prostatic hyperplasia, 1999 February 12 (Box 42, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 41-107 - SAMe for depression, 1999 November 5 (Box 42, Folder 4-7)
- TML, 41-3 - Palivizumab (Synagis) for prevention of RSV infection, 1999 January 1 (Box 42, Folder 8-9)
- TML, 41:47 - Generic Drugs, 1999 May 21 (Box 42, Folder 10-15)
- TML, 41-64 - Amprenavir - a new HIV protease inhibitor, 1999 July 16 (Box 42, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 41-75 - Antimicrobial prophylaxis in surgery, 1999 August 27 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- TML, 41-75 - Antimicrobial prophylaxis in surgery, 1999 August 27 (Box 43, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 41-95 - The Choice of antibacterial drugs, 1999 October 22 (Box 43, Folder 4-8)